http://www.buildingscience.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Our ServicesForensic InvestigationsBuilding Performance and Enclosure ConsultingEducation and TrainingResearch, Development and DemonstrationArticles and PapersBuilding Science InsightsBuilding Science DigestsPublished ArticlesConference PapersResearch ReportsBuilding America ReportsGuidanceDesigns That WorkEnclosures That WorkGuides & ManualsInformation SheetsPopular TopicsCrawlspacesHigh R-value RetrofitsFoundations and SlabsUnvented Roof/AtticHigh R-value wallsVapor BarriersBookstoreBuilder's GuidesBuilding EnclosuresControlling MoistureVentilationEvents and TrainingBuilding Science FundamentalsRenovation and RehabilitationUpcoming Other EventsPast Events
You are hereHome » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Policy last updated: Friday, December 11, 2020 - 1:31am We appreciate the trust you place in Building Science Corporation, and we are committed to respecting your privacy and the security of your personal information. This privacy policy describes the information that we collect and how we use it.INFORMATION WE COLLECTWe may collect information (including name, address, telephone number, project details, and email address) when you:Sign up for our newsletterInquire about our servicesSign up for updatesEnter a contest or sweepstakesAre referred to us through a marketing promotionParticipate in a marketing survey, promotion or eventWe maintain the data that you provide us in a secure database. We also gather information about how visitors navigate through our Web site by using clickstream data gathered with "cookies" and/or other online tools such as "pixel tags." See Cookies and Pixel Tags below for further information. WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?At Building Science Corporation, we always want to provide you with the best possible experience and fulfill your needs exactly as you've requested. In order to do this, we collect information that allows us to:Provide the services you requestContact you about an inquirySend you Building Science Corporation email updatesCustomize our communications to youINFORMATION WE SHARE WITH OTHERS AND YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTSWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.YOUR CHOICES ABOUT COMMUNICATION FROM Building Science Corp.We offer choices about the types of information you receive from us. If you prefer not to receive email updates or newsletters from us please follow the unsubscribe using the link provided in each edition of the email, or please contact us at info@buildingscience.com or atBuilding Science Corporation70 Main St, Westford, MA 01886Please be sure to provide us your exact name and email address so that we can be sure to identify you correctly.HOW WE USE EMAILWhen you provide us your email address, we will email you as necessary to respond to a request for or inquiry about our services, or to provide ongoing customer service. We may also send promotional email about products, special offers, services or events that we believe may be of interest to you. It is our intent to send promotional emails only to those persons who wish to receive them. We provide instructions on how to unsubscribe in each email.COOKIES AND PIXEL TAGSA cookie is a small data file that is stored by your Web browser on your computer. Cookies enable you to place an order on our Website. They also allow us to enhance and personalize your online experience, so that the information you receive is more relevant to you.We also use pixel tags – tiny graphic images – to tell us what parts of our Web site you have visited or to measure the effectiveness of any searches you may do on our site. Pixel tags also enable us to send you email in a format you can read and let us know when you have opened an email message from us. We may also contract with other companies who use cookies or other online tools such as pixel tags to measure the performance of a marketing effort on our behalf. We prohibit these companies from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone but us.LINKS TO OTHER SITESOccasionally we provide links on our Web site to other sites we think you will enjoy. These sites operate independently of Building Science Corp., and have established their own privacy and security policies. For the best online experience, we strongly encourage you to review these policies at any site you visit.PRIVACY OF CHILDREN ON OUR WEBSITEOur Web site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.POLICY CHANGESFrom time to time, we may use customer information for unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change, we will post these changes on our Website. We encourage you to review our privacy policy periodically.QUESTIONS OR COMMENTS?We always welcome your questions and feedback. For privacy-related issues, please contact us at:Building Science Corporation70 Main St, Westford, MA 01886info@buildingscience.com
